{
  "heading": "Addition and Subtraction of Like Fractions.",
  "topics": [
    {
      "heading": "Addition and Subtraction of Like Fractions.",
      "questions": [
        {
            "questionNo": 1,
            "question": "Mr. Johnson cut a large piece of paper into 45/47 pieces for the invites. If 36/47 of the paper was used for the first batch of invites, how much paper is remaining?",
            "options": [
                "8/47",
                "9/47",
                "10/47",
                "11/47"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 2,
            "question": "Lily had 25/60 of her invitations ready. What is the simplest form of this fraction?",
            "options": [
                "1/12",
                "12/5",
                "1/5",
                "5/12"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 3,
            "question": "Ben used 44/48 of his paper for invitations. Simplify this fraction.",
            "options": [
                "11/12",
                "12/11",
                "1/12",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 4,
            "question": "Lily and Ben prepared 19/67 of their invitations by the end of the first day. They managed to send out 8/67 of them. How many invitations do they still need to send?",
            "options": [
                "9/67",
                "10/67",
                "11/67",
                "12/67"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 5,
            "question": "Lily and Ben each prepared 2/4 of an invitation. How much of an invitation did they prepare together?",
            "options": [
                "1/4",
                "2/4",
                "4/4",
                "3/4"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 6,
            "question": "Ben discovered he made 30/54 of the invitations incorrectly. What is this fraction in simplest form?",
            "options": [
                "5/9",
                "1/5",
                "9/5",
                "1/9"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 7,
            "question": "At the art festival, they used 76/50 of a large roll of ribbon. If 41/50 of the ribbon was used for decorations, how much ribbon is left?",
            "options": [
                "32/50",
                "33/50",
                "34/50",
                "35/50"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 8,
            "question": "Mr. Johnson cut 45/50 of a sheet for the extra invites. Simplify this fraction.",
            "options": [
                "9/5",
                "8/10",
                "1/10",
                "9/10"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 9,
            "question": "If Mr. Johnson cuts 11/97 of a sheet for Lily, 42/97 for Ben, and another 26/97 for extra invites, how much of the sheet did he cut in total?",
            "options": [
                "76/97",
                "77/97",
                "79/97",
                "78/97"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 10,
            "question": "Lily realized that 27/48 of her invitation was unnecessary. Simplify the fraction.",
            "options": [
                "1/16",
                "5/16",
                "8/16",
                "9/16"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 11,
            "question": "Lily has 50/80 of a sheet of decorative paper. She receives another 45/80 sheet from Ben. After using 43/80 of a sheet for her project, how much decorative paper does she have left?",
            "options": [
                "51/80",
                "52/80",
                "41/80",
                "54/80"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 12,
            "question": "Lily has 23/71 of a sheet of decorative paper left after her project. She uses 16/71 of it to make a card. How much of the sheet does she have left?",
            "options": [
                "7/71",
                "1/71",
                "6/71",
                "2/71"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 13,
            "question": "Mr. Johnson helped Lily and Ben by cutting 45/31​ of a sheet of paper for Lily and 21/31​ for Ben. How much of the sheet did he cut in total?",
            "options": [
                "60/31",
                "66/31",
                "70/31",
                "63/31"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 14,
            "question": "Ben has 9/26 of a jar of marbles. He buys another 11/26 of a jar of marbles at the store. After giving away 11/20 of the marbles to his friend, how many marbles does Ben have left?",
            "options": [
                "8/20",
                "9/20",
                "10/20",
                "7/20"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 15,
            "question": "Mr. Johnson cut 15/25 of a sheet for Lily. What is this fraction in simplest form?",
            "options": [
                "3/5",
                "4/5",
                "5/5",
                "2/5"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 16,
            "question": "Ben had 35/62 of a large piece of construction paper. He gave 24/62 of it to Lily. How much of the construction paper does Ben have now?",
            "options": [
                "10/62",
                "11/62",
                "12/62",
                "13/62"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 17,
            "question": "If Lily added the 9/20 paper of the invitation to the 12/20 she already prepared, how much of the invitation does she have now?",
            "options": [
                "21/20",
                "22/20",
                "19/20",
                "23/20"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 18,
            "question": "Lily realized that 27/63 of the invitations were damaged. Simplify this fraction.",
            "options": [
                "1/7",
                "2/7",
                "3/7",
                "4/7"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 19,
            "question": "Lily and Ben prepared 36/82 of an invitation. What is the fraction in its simplest form?",
            "options": [
                "17/41",
                "18/41",
                "19/41",
                "20/41"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ]
    
    
    }
  ]
}
